RESUME OBJECTIVE

Software Engineer with knowledge of coding languages (e.g. Scala, Java, JavaScript) and frameworks/systems (e.g. Angular, Git). Knowledge in databases and Object-Relational Mapping (ORM) frameworks (e.g. Hibernate). Experience as frontend developer. Familiarity with Agile development methodologies and ability to learn new languages and technologies.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Ceiba Software House, Medellin, Colombia / April 2018 – December 2018 Corporate insurance sales system - Sura

- Understanding customer requirements.
- Explaining system feature
- Producing clean and efficient code based on specifications (Scala and Angular5)
- Testing and deploying programs and systems
- Fixing and improving existing software
- Integrate software components and third-party systems (Git)
- Verify and deploy systems in Jenkins
- Worked in an agile approach, attending daily scrum, working in twoweek sprints using JIRA to update task.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Sura, Medellín, Colombia / March 2017 – March 2018

- Researching, designing, implementing and managing software (Java, Scala and AngularJs)
- Identifying areas for modification in existing software and subsequently developing these modifications.
- Maintaining and upgrading existing systems
- Working closely with other developers, UX designers, business and systems analysts

REFERENCES

Available on request

CONTACTS

Email:

lauris037.lm@gmail.com **Phone:** +61 433670392 **Address:** 2005/ 280

Spencer St, Melbourne, VIC

3000

SOCIAL MEDIA

f laurita.m03

lauritam03

in Imarulanda

SKILLS

JavaScript

Java

PL/SQL

Scala

HTML5

CSS

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

University of Medellin, Colombia

2010 - 2018

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English